<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Lil Sidekick</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="SplashScreenTitle">JWAKE App Title Here!!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home_screen">HomeScreen</string>

    <string name="title_section1">User</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Account</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Home</string>
    <string name="title_section4">About</string>
    <string name="title_section5">Options</string>
    <string name="title_section6">Logout</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>
    <string name="introparagraph">
        Hello, I am your sidekick! My goal is to serve as a guide for parents to teach their
        children to become independent! Autistic children are often ill-prepared to take care of
        themselves by the time they finish their education and come of age. Their education usually
        does not provide them with many important daily skills that your child will need to take
        care of himself and participate as a member of society. Together, we can better prepare your
        child to become an independent individual who can take on the world. I will provide you with
        a guide on what needs to be improved while you supervise your child’s training process and
        monitor his improvement. The earlier we start, the better!
    </string>
    <string name="aboutparagraph">
        The goal of My Lil Sidekick is to serve as a guide for parents to teach their
        children to become independent. Autistic children are often ill-prepared to take care of
        themselves by the time they finish their education and come of age. Their education usually
        does not provide them with many important daily skills that your child will need to take
        care of himself and participate as a member of society. You will be provided with
        guidance on what needs to be improved while you supervise your child’s training process and
        monitor his improvement as he grows closer to becoming an independent individual. The earlier
        you start, the better!
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_make_account">MakeAccount</string>
    <string name="title_activity_activity_screen">activity_screen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_end_task">EndTask</string>
    <string name="title_activity_results_screen">ResultsScreen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_task_instruction">TaskInstructions</string>

    <string name="title_activity_about_screen">AboutScreen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_records_screen">RecordsScreen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_struggle_question_screen">StruggleQuestionScreen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_introduction_screen">Welcome!</string>


</resources>
